MARIANNA POGHOSYAN

France, Marseille • +33769893460 • poghosyan.may@gmail.com

www.poghosyan.me



Front-End Developer

Summary

Over the last 5 years, I have developed a wide range of websites using HTML, CSS, Javascript, jQuery, Bootstrap, Sass, Vue.js, React.js, Git, PHP, MySQL and PSD for mock-ups including sites for startup companies and businesses. My core competency lies in complete end to end management of a new website development project, and I am seeking opportunities to build websites from the ground up for your business or for you web presence.

-

Experience and Skills

Graphic Design	UI/UX Design	Frontend	Backend
Photoshop	Sketch	JavaScript	 PHP (OOP, MVC,
 Illustrator 	 WebFlow 	jQuery	design patterns)
 InDesign 	 MockFlow 	Vue.js	 Unit/Functional
 Procreate 	 InVision Studio 	• React.js	testing
• Canva	 Balsamiq 	• HTML5	• SQL
• Wacom	• Proto.io	CSS3(LESS, SASS)Twitter Bootstrap	VCS
		 MDBootstrap 	 Git (Github, Gitlab, Gitbucket, Assembla)

Work experience

09/2018 - Present	Front-end Developer & UI/UX Designer Freelancer
03/2019 - 09/19	CEO Founder Way2Up LLC
09/2017 - 09/2018	Front-end Developer CoriseUp LLC
01/2016 - 08/2017	Front - End Developer & SMM Coderiders LLC

10/2015 - 08/2017	Social Media Marketing Manager Coderiders LLC			
10/2014 - 05/2015	Graphic Designer and Social Marketing Manager WebSoft LLC			
Education				
08/2015 - 10/2015	Web Development School Coderiders LLC After 2 months of learning courses, started to work in the company and continued to learn as a worker			
2012 - 2016	BSc (Hons) in Computer Science National Polytechnic University of Armenia			
2009 - 2012	Math & Physics Armenia, Yerevan, 195 High School			

